ELIZABETH GLEASON

UX Designer





Buffalo, NY



libbyelliott@hotmail.co.uk

PROFILE

I am a User Experience designer with a background in Human Factors and Industrial Design. In my current role I contribute to all phases of product development including user research, wire framing and mockups, usability testing, prototyping and post release feedback. Working with an agile, continuous discovery methodology allows me to understand and meet the needs of users, delivering solutions that make a positive impact within our applications

EDUCATION



Master of Science -Human Factors Loughborough University, UK

Bachelor of Arts Hons -Industrial Design and Technology Loughborough University, UK

KEY SKILLS



Sketch

Figma

Omnigraffle

AppCues



User Research / Interviews
Continuous Discovery
Usability Testing
Accessibility Audits
Task Analysis
Wireframes and Mockups

WORK EXPERIENCE

Anthology Buffalo, NY - 2018 - Present

Senior UX Designer

Working on various applications for higher education

- User Interviews and research
- Lead UX designer on Continuous Discovery product team
- Wire frames and mockups
- Usability studies
- Create personas
- User journeys
- Conduct accessibility audits
- Generate in app feedback

StraussGroup Buffalo, NY - 2018

Executive Search Consultant

- Ran 360 desk
- Business development
- Recruiting for UI/UX Designers

Iroquois Central School District Elma, NY - 2015 - 2018

Teacher Aide

English Tea Ladies Elma, NY 2009 - 2016

Owner of catering business

QINETIQ (formerly Defence Evaluation Research Agency)

Farnborough, UK - 2001 - 2006

Lead Human Factors Consultant and Assistant Design Lead

- HF Evaluations of all land platforms in the British Army.
- Wrote Human Factors Integration Management plan (HFIMP) for US DoD and London Underground
- Human factors assessment and testing of prototypes
- Conducted extensive task analysis.
- Project manager for sleep study.
- HF Evaluations Assessment of British Navy equipment